Now we should feel very comfortable with a lot of words and phrases related to time and duration prepositions
现在我们应该对很多与时间和持续时间介词相关的单词和短语感到很舒服
that are very common.
这很常见。
Let's now get into a little bit more complexity although still pretty easy.
现在让我们更复杂一点，虽然仍然很容易。
Still pretty basic and how we can talk about a range a range of times you've probably seen this before.
仍然很基本，我们如何谈论一系列你可能以前见过的范围。
When should we use from to when should we use.
我们什么时候应该使用从到什么时候应该使用。
Between and they mean the same thing.
之间和他们的意思是一样的。
It's just about how you use them from goes with to between goes with N..
这只是关于你如何使用它们，从 go with 到 between go with N..
Just remember that and you're pretty much OK.
只要记住这一点，你就可以了。
You can use it to talk about both of these to talk about months years times.
你可以用它来谈论这两个来谈论几个月几年的时间。
So it's extremely useful as long as you feel comfortable using these.
因此，只要您对使用这些感到自在，它就非常有用。
We're talking about a range beginning here now that I know that a lot of the ending here.
我们现在谈论的是从这里开始的范围，因为我知道这里有很多结尾。
OK so let's try it from June 8th 2014 to July 17th 2014.
好的，让我们从 2014 年 6 月 8 日到 2014 年 7 月 17 日试一试。
The Web site will be down OK from June 8 2014 to July 17th 2014.
该网站将在 2014 年 6 月 8 日至 2014 年 7 月 17 日期间正常关闭。
The Web site will be down.
该网站将关闭。
One thing we can do here when we're talking about this range this range when the Web site will be down
当我们谈论这个范围时，我们可以在这里做的一件事是当网站关闭时这个范围
or not working is that we can notice the year here and here these two are the same if they're different
或不工作是我们可以注意到这里和这里的年份如果它们不同，这两个是相同的
we have to say both.
我们不得不说两者。
In fact we can probably leave out the second one and we usually do that when we're reading a list of
事实上，我们可能会忽略第二个，我们通常在阅读列表时这样做
things which has the same noun for each one.
每个事物都有相同的名词。
I want to eat Italian food Spanish food French food and Indian food.
我想吃意大利菜西班牙菜法国菜和印度菜。
Or we could just say one of those I want to eat Italian French Indian and Spanish food.
或者我们可以说其中一个我想吃意大利法式印度和西班牙食物。
OK.
好的。
Now for this one we could go from June 8th to July 17th 2014.
现在对于这个，我们可以从 2014 年 6 月 8 日到 7 月 17 日。
The Web site will be down from June 8th 2000 14th to July 17th.
该网站将从2000 年6 月8 日14 日至7 月17 日关闭。
The Web site will be down.
该网站将关闭。
That's OK too.
那也没关系。
That's OK.
没关系。
2 for for things like food it would be the second one or the last one and for the dates or the times
2 对于食物之类的东西，它将是第二个或最后一个，对于日期或时间
it can be it can be either one honestly.
老实说，它可以是任何一个。
Now how can we do this with between an end.
现在我们如何才能做到这一点。
Well it's it's pretty easy.
嗯，这很容易。
I would say between between June 8th 2014 and July 17th that's it.
我想说的是在 2014 年 6 月 8 日到 7 月 17 日之间。
Everything else is the same.
其他一切都是一样的。
So it's exactly the same.
所以它是完全一样的。
The only difference is this one has two and this one has and they're both talking about a period of
唯一的区别是这个有两个，这个有，他们都在谈论一段时期
time.
时间。
Now let's let's just do a quick example with actual times we are only open from 4:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m.
现在让我们做一个简单的例子，我们只从下午 4:00 开始营业。到晚上 7:00
And if someone is speaking this they probably won't say p.m. they'll probably just say we are only open
如果有人这么说，他们可能不会说下午。他们可能只会说我们只开放
from four to seven because no place is open from 4:00 a.m. to 7:00 a.m..
从四点到七点，因为凌晨 4:00 到 7:00 没有地方开放。
Well maybe some fast food restaurants.
好吧，也许是一些快餐店。
We could also then say we are only open between four and seven.
我们也可以说我们只在四点到七点之间开放。
You get the idea.
你明白了。
You get the idea pretty simple pretty basic same thing four years from 2013 to two thousand eighteen.
从 2013 年到 2018 年的四年，你的想法很简单，基本相同。
Then you can say something that happened.
然后你可以说发生了什么事。
Mary was living in Canada.
玛丽住在加拿大。
Whatever you want to say there.
不管你想在那里说什么。
OK.
好的。
So this is pretty simple.
所以这很简单。
Exactly the same.
完全相同的。
Just need to remember which one goes with and which one goes with two.
只需要记住哪个和哪个一起去，哪个和两个一起去。